[{"id": 2670, "question": "One day while shopping in a small town in southern California,it was my misfortune to be approached by a clerk whose personality conflicted with mine. He seemed most unfriendly and not at all concerned about my intended purchase. I bought nothing,and marched angrily out of the store. My hostility toward that clerk increased with each step. On the outside,standing by the road,was a darkskinned young man in his early twenties. His expressive brown eyes met and held mine,and in the next instant a beautiful, dazzling smile covered his face. I gave way immediately. The magnetic power of that smile dissolved all bitterness within me,and I found the muscles in my own face happily responding . \"Beautiful day,isn't it?\"I remarked,in passing. Then,I turned back.\"I really owe you a debt of gratitude ...\n\nQ: In the passage, the author seems to suggest that we should   _  .", "options": ["be generous to strangers", "practice smiling every day", "smile at other people", "help people in trouble"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 536, "question": "Two studies are suggesting that some overweight people do not face an increased risk of developing heart disease. Researchers also found that some individuals of normal body weight have an increased risk of the disease. Being overweight does increase your risk of medical problems, but the studies found that not all heavy people are less healthy than thin people. In one study, American researchers examined medical records from over 5000 men and women. Each person had taken part in a separate study from 1999 to 2004. The searchers found that about 51% of them were overweight or obese. About 32% were obese, but considered metabolically healthy. This means they had no evidence of problems in tests for high blood pressure or other factors linked to heart disease. However, more than 23% of peopl...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about evidence that some people can  _  .", "options": ["be both fat and healthy", "develop heart disease", "increase weight", "have too much fat in the liver"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3461, "question": "Manage your time well for each module , but also make sure you get a good balance between work and social life. That is for life in general. Set aside time specifically for each subject. Try to study one subject a day. You need to balance time. If you are bad at balancing things, make a personal timetable. Even if you do not stick to it, you will have an idea what you should be doing each day. This is better than trying to do everything each day and, at the end of the week, not achieve anything. Also, try to keep your weekends free of studying. Only study at the weekend if you really have to. I had to learn to balance work, study and family when I was at college. I was a retail assistant working part-time and had at least four modules to complete at the same time at college. I also had to ...\n\nQ: It could be inferred from the passage that   _   .", "options": ["the writer has a part-time job as an assistant when he was at college", "you need to set a timetable for yourself", "you should make a personal timetable if you are bad at balancing your time", "the writer can arrange his time well when he was at college"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3481, "question": "A few years ago, I moved into a new house in Los Angeles. Soon after, a family moved in next door. It wasn't the best of times for me. I had just divorced from my second wife, and I wasn't working. I'd come home each day and sit by myself in the backyard. One night, I heard someone from the yard next door, \"Tom ! How are you, Tom? \" I couldn't see anybody through the trees, but I answered, \"I' m good.\" \"Good!\" said the voice. \"What's your name?\" I asked. \"Eric.\" Then I heard someone say, \"Eric, don't bother him.\" \"Okay!\" Eric said. \"Talk to you tomorrow!\" Months later, on Halloween, we finally met face to face. Eric came to the door dressed like a rap star. We became friends. We'd hang out in our yards, and Eric, who was almost 17 at the time and look liked a 13-year-old, would tell me his...\n\nQ: The writer of this passage is a(an)_.", "options": ["teacher", "actor", "singer", "doctor"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 559, "question": "EDGEWOOD-Every morning at Dixie Heights High School, customers pour into a special experiment: the district's first coffee shop run mostly by students with special learning needs. Well before classes start, students and teachers order Lattes, Cappuccinos and Hot Chocolates. Then, during the first period, teachers call in orders on their room phones, and students make deliveries. By closing time at 9.20 a.m., the shop usually sells 90 drinks. \"Whoever made the chi tea, Ms. Schatzman says it was good,\" Christy McKinley, a second year student, announced recently, after hanging up with the teacher. The shop is called the Dixie PIT, which stands for Power in Transition. Although some of the students are not disabled, many are, and the PIT helps them prepare for life after high school. They lear...\n\nQ: Where can we usually read this passage?", "options": ["In a novel.", "In a newspaper.", "In an instant message.", "In a school report."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3482, "question": "A few years ago, I moved into a new house in Los Angeles. Soon after, a family moved in next door. It wasn't the best of times for me. I had just divorced from my second wife, and I wasn't working. I'd come home each day and sit by myself in the backyard. One night, I heard someone from the yard next door, \"Tom ! How are you, Tom? \" I couldn't see anybody through the trees, but I answered, \"I' m good.\" \"Good!\" said the voice. \"What's your name?\" I asked. \"Eric.\" Then I heard someone say, \"Eric, don't bother him.\" \"Okay!\" Eric said. \"Talk to you tomorrow!\" Months later, on Halloween, we finally met face to face. Eric came to the door dressed like a rap star. We became friends. We'd hang out in our yards, and Eric, who was almost 17 at the time and look liked a 13-year-old, would tell me his...\n\nQ: What do we learn about Eric from the passage?", "options": ["He lives alone with his father.", "He has a very rich father", "He often feels very lonely.", "He is a rap star."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2770, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time....\n\nQ: This passage aims to    _   .", "options": ["make comments on films for a cinema", "introduce films for a film corporation", "recommend several films for fun", "advertise several films for a website"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1133, "question": "We are not rich by what we possess but rather by what we can do without. ----Immauel Kant Many times my friend June would say, \"If I ever get rich, I'm getting a completely new wardrobe and moving into a bigger apartment.\" I thought of her words and her chances of being rich are about as good as mine. But, to everyone's surprise, a few years ago June did come to large inheritance . At first June said very little about the money. As the initial shock disappeared, she became excited, June is a great believer in making lists, so I was surprised to find her writing down all the ways she would spend her new wealth. As time went on, she started revising the list. What had been midway down the list was now at the top. At last, I said to her, \"You know, it isn't necessary to spend all your inherit...\n\nQ: What did the writer think of her friend's new decision?", "options": ["She found it funny and wrong.", "She found it unacceptable and unbelievable.", "She found it surprising and meaningful.", "She found it difficult and meaningless."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3435, "question": "A quarter of US adults say they read no books at all in the past year, according to an Associated Press-Ipsos survey. The typical person said that he / she read four books in the last year and, excluding those who had not read any books at all, the usual number of books read was seven. Of those who did read, women and pensioners were the most eager readers, and religious works and popular fiction were the top choices. The number of books read was nine books for women and five for men. The number also showed that those with college degrees read the most, and people aged 50 and over read more than those who are younger. People from the West and Midwest are more likely to have read at least one book in the past year. Southerners who do read tend to read more books -- mostly religious books an...\n\nQ: Which kind of Americans read the most last year according to the survey?", "options": ["Older men with college degrees from the South.", "Older women with college degrees from the South.", "Younger educated men from the Midwest.", "Younger educated women from the West."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2473, "question": "My mother used to ask me what the most important part of the body is. Through the years Iwould take a guess at what I thought was the correct answer. When I was younger, I thought sound was very important to us as humans, so I said: \"My ears, Mommy.\" She said: \"No. Many people are deaf. But you keep thinking about it and I will ask you again soon.\"Several years passed before she asked me again. Since making my first attempt, I had contemplated the correct answer. So this time I told her: \"Mommy, sight is very important to everybody, so it must be our eyes.\" She looked at me and told me: \"You are learning fast, but the answer is not correct because there are many people who are blind.\" Mother asked me a couple more times and always her answer was \"No. But you are getting smarter every year,...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the article?", "options": ["The author was becoming smarter by answering the question.", "The mother wanted the author to be both loving and loved.", "The mother was trying to train the author to think on his or her own.", "The author didn't think the mother's answer was correct."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3079, "question": "One summer day as I was heading to the teaching building I heard someone call my name. I turned around and I saw Philip ,a counselor at our admissions office , standing with another young man, Philip introduced me to him, Stephen, and reminded me that Stephen would be taking one of my classes. Stephen looked at me. With a somewhat painful expression, he asked if my class was going to be hard and if he would be able to pass. I introduced all the things that he would be expected to learn. As we talked, I saw Stephen's eyes getting big with fear. I told him to do all of his assignments, and to hand them in on time. Rather than being overwhelmed by all of the work, I told him the most successful students made a master calendar of all the assignments so they could plan their workload. As the fa...\n\nQ: What lesson can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["A good beginning is a half done.", "One bite at a time", "Haste(n.) makes waste", "Look before you leap(v. )."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1104, "question": "\"Family\" is of course an _ word. But when British people say that their society is based on family life, they are thinking of \"family\" in its narrow, peculiarly European sense of mother ,father and children living together alone in their own house as an economic and social unit. Thus, every British marriage indicates the beginning of a new and independent family--hence the tremendous importance of marriage in British life. For both the man and the woman, marriage means leaving one's parents and starting one's own life. The man's first duty will then be to his wife, and the wife's to her husband. He will be entirely responsible for her financial support, and she for the running of the new home. Their children will be their common responsibility and theirs alone. Neither the wife's parents n...\n\nQ: For an English family, the husband's duty is   _  .", "options": ["supporting the family while the wife is financial", "defending the family while the wife is running the home", "financial while the wife is running the home", "independent while the wife is dependent"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2630, "question": "Men sometimes say: \"We are better and cleverer than women. Women never invented things. We do.\" It is true that men have invented a lot of useful things: the alphabet, machines, rockets, and guns, too. But scientists and archeologists now agree that women invented one very important thing. It had changed the history. They invented agriculture. Before the invention of agriculture men were hunter. They went out every day. Sometimes they killed animals-sometimes animals killed them. Life was difficult and dangerous. Women had to go out every day, too. They collected roots, fruit and grass. Then, one day, more than 10,000years ago a woman dropped some grass seeds. She dropped them near her home in the Middle East. They grew--and the first wheat was born. The idea grew, too. Women planted roots...\n\nQ: Which one do you believe according to the passage?", "options": ["Women are better and cleverer than men.", "Women invented many useful things like men.", "Women played a very important part in agriculture.", "Women were great in civilization."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 423, "question": "Do you love holidays but hate gaining weight? You are not alone. Holidays are times for celebrating. Many people are worried about their weight. With proper planning, though, it is possible to keep normal weight during the holidays. The idea is to enjoy the holidays but not to eat too much. You don't have to turn away from the foods that you enjoy. Here are some tips for preventing weight gain and maintaining physical fitness: Don't skip meals. Before you leave home, have a small, low-fat meal or snack . This may help to avoid getting too excited before delicious foods. Control the amount of food. Use a small plate that may encourage you to \"load up \". You should be most comfortable eating an amount of food about the size of your fist . Begin with soup and fruit or vegetables. Fill up befo...\n\nQ: Many people can't control their weight during the holidays mainly because they   _  .", "options": ["can't help eating too much", "take part in too many parties", "enjoy delicious foods sometimes", "can't help turning away from foods."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1913, "question": "When we look at the sky and see a bright light moving quickly across it or coming towards the earth, we talk about seeing a \"shooting star\" or a \"falling star\". These moving lights are not, in fact, stars at all. They are small pieces of matter from outer space, which burn up as they enter the Earth's atmosphere. The correct name of them is meteoroids. Any pieces that make it to the Earth's surface without completely burning up are known as meteorites. A meteor is actually the name given to the light we see when a meteoroid is burning up. When a meteorite hits the Earth at speeds between 11 and 72 kilometers a second, it can do amazing damage. A very large meteorite could knock the earth out of its orbit. If this happened, all life on Earth would probably become extinct . The path we follo...\n\nQ: Some scientists believe the dinosaurs became extinct because   _  .", "options": ["they were hit by meteors", "meteorites landed on their nests", "meteorites landed and changed the climate", "they could no longer breathe the atmosphere"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1733, "question": "Throughout July 1945, the Japanese mainland, from Tokyo on Honshu northward to the coast of Hokkaido, were bombed as if an invasion were about to take place. In fact, something far more threatening was at hand, as the Americans were telling Stalin at Potsdam. In 1939 physicists in the United States had learned of experiments in Germany showing the possibility of atomic power and understood the coming damage of an atomic bomb. On August 2, 1939, Albert Einstein warned President Roosevelt of the danger of Nazi Germany's advances in development of the atomic bomb. Eventually, the U.S. Office of Scientific Research Development was created in June 1941 and given combined responsibility with the War Department in the Manhattan Project to develop a nuclear bomb. After four years of research and d...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["An atomic bomb was dropped on Hiroshima and Nagasaki.", "After research and development efforts, an atomic bomb was born.", "An invasion was about to take place with the use of the atomic bomb.", "The birth and use of the atomic bomb ended the Second World War."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 323, "question": "Now I know that we black people are much more likely to have high blood pressure and diabetes than white people. And _ often lead to heart attacks and other untreated diseases. For example, black people are three to four times more likely than white people to have high blood pressure and twice as likely as the white population to die of a stroke . New research has found out the surprisingly high levels of salt in many of black people's favorite meals. I stopped putting extra salt in my food at the table long ago and I try to cut down on the salt I use in cooking. The recommended daily level of salt for adults is 6 grams. It is easy to see that if you avoid processed foods and use salt in your cooking within the limit, you won't exceed the daily level. The research showed how much salt ther...\n\nQ: The researcher provided curry goat and rice and peas in order to   _  .", "options": ["thank those who came to his home for his research", "let people know that eating less salt makes one healthier", "show that tasty food with less salt can be made at home", "prove the less salt the food has the more delicious it is"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2444, "question": "It's not easy to find a person with the qualities it takes to be a hero. I didn't really understand the meaning of the word \"hero\" until my third year in the college. If you saw her, you wouldn't think she really looks the part, but she is stronger than Superman could ever be. Her name is Sandra Keierleber. I first met her at volleyball tryouts , but didn't notice anything special at first. As the week passed, however, she showed she had more heart than anyone. She stood out because she never gave up, no matter what. Sandra isn't the tallest or the fastest --- in fact, this was her first time playing volleyball and it showed--- but that didn't stop her. She was always the first to arrive and the last to leave. By the end of tryouts she had found a place in everyone's heart. When the name l...\n\nQ: Sandra began to play volleyball when   _  .", "options": ["she was tall enough", "she was at college", "she became a hero", "she met the Superman"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2261, "question": "From Nigerian science fiction to a time-travelling serial killer, Brittle Paper selects the best works of fiction from the continent to inspire our inner desire to travel. My Life in the Bush of Ghosts - Amos Tutuola Who wouldn't want to get enveloped in a fog of magical delight? The novel describes the adventures of a little boy lost in a forest. His search for the way back home seem to take him deeper and deeper into secret colonies of creatures living in reality. Nigerians in Space - Deji Olukotun Wale is a Nigerian lunar geologist. He is under the spell of a life-long dream to traveling out to the moon when the mysterious Mr Bello offers him the chance to man a Nigerian space-exploration mission. But like most dreams, what starts out as the magical fulfillment of desire quickly slips i...\n\nQ: We can infer from the novels that  _", "options": ["Amos Tutuola tells a story of ghosts", "Sissie wins a world travel scholarship", "Deji Olukotum made his dream of traveling to the moon come true.", "The Moor's Account indeed talks about a journey of heart"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1870, "question": "I recall a moment that I experienced with my dad when I was twenty-one. I was going to college and living with a couple of friends in Chicago. When the car I was using died, my dad, realizing that I needed transportation to get to work and to school, was good enough to lend me the money for a used car. Shortly after I bought it, my parents drove down to San Diego for the winter. Before they left, my dad gave me some of his bank deposit slips with clear and detailed instructions to put one hundred dollars of my earnings, every payday, into their savings account while they were gone. At that time of my life, I was not yet clear about what were the most important problems that I had to attend to first. I dismissed our agreement as nothing important and continued to spend my money as fast as I...\n\nQ: When dealing with the writer's failure to keep his word, his father was   _  .", "options": ["mild but unfair", "angry but considerate", "firm but forgiving", "cruel but reasonable"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2410, "question": "Wang Lu, 24, one of many students studying abroad who'll come home for work, majors in business & management studies at Edinburgh's Napier University. She had planned what to do after graduation in the UK: two years' work experience at a restaurant and a tour around Europe. But now her plans are up in the air. Following the UK Home Secretary's meeting on reform of the student immigration system, the UK government recently announced the end of the post-study work visa from April 2012. This will force tens of thousands of Chinese students to leave the UK after graduation. Sadly, the domestic job market doesn't welcome them with open arms. A report by Tigtag.com at the end of 2011 showed that over 35 percent of students admitted that they have employment problems. \"Returning students often ha...\n\nQ: Where can we most probably read this text?", "options": ["In a science fiction.", "In a travel magazine.", "In a newspaper.", "In a student's book."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1064, "question": "Why do people cross their fingers when facing difficulties-eve non-religious people? Why do we blame the black cat when we saw the low score of the test? These habits have been referred to as magical thinking and can be found everywhere in daily life. For example, a person wishes something bad for an annoying colleague. Or parents pray for a safe fight when seeing their son off. Psychologically helpful In examining these habits, scientists decided to search for a reason for humans' belief in magical powers. Psychologists have their own approach to the question. \"I think in part it's because we are constantly exposed to our own thoughts, and thus likely to overestimate their connection to outside events. \"said Emily Pronin, a psychologist in the prefix = st1 /US. For people who are uncertai...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the next?", "options": ["Justin Barrett, an evolutionist, denies magical thinking is a product of adaptation.", "People with a weak faith have a better chance of surviving competition.", "The adaptationists think we are born with a tendency to believe in our magic thinking.", "Dr. Daniel Wegner believe magic thinking can be a great help."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1184, "question": "A recent study, published in last week's Journal of the American Medical Association, offers a picture of how risky it is to get a lift from a teenage driver. Indeed, a 16-year-old driver with three or more passengers is three times as likely to have a deadly accident as a teenager driving alone, while the risk of death for drivers between 30 and 59 decreases with each additional passenger. The authors also found that the death rates for teenage drivers increased sharply after 10 p.m., and especially after midnight. With passengers in the car, the driver was even more likely to die in a late-night accident. Robert Foss, a scientist at the University of North Carolina Highway Safety Research Center, says the higher death rates for teenage drivers have less to do with \"really stupid behavior...\n\nQ: Which of the following situations can we infer is most dangerous according to the passage?", "options": ["A teenager driving after midnight with passengers in the car.", "Adults giving a lift to teenagers on the highway after 10 p.m.", "Adults driving with three or more teenage passengers late at night.", "A teenager getting a lift from a stranger on the highway at midnight."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3413, "question": "Welcome to Arundel Castle which is situated in West Sussex, England. The castle has a history of nearly 1000 years and has welcomed visitors traveling from all over the world. Arundel Castle also plays a starring role in many films. _ The White Garden is planted with soft white Iceberg Roses, and Snow White Lilies. The Rose Garden is newly planted with lovely old-fashioned English roses that are at their very best in June and July. The Organic Kitchen Garden produces a wide range of seasonal fruit and vegetables, pears, cherries and apples. _ In the Castle Shop, you will discover a wide and interesting range of gift ideas for everyone. It offers gifts and souvenirs designed to appeal to all tastes and pockets. Foods, china, books, and stationery are all available. Many are sold in this Cas...\n\nQ: How long does the Arundel Festival last this year?", "options": ["10 days", "One week", "16 days", "One month"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 345, "question": "A new survey finds that more than eighty percent of Internet users in the United States search for health information online. The survey found that searching online is one of the leading ways that people look for a second opinion though doctors are still the main source of health information. Forty-four percent of people are actually looking for doctors or other providers when they search for health information online. Another finding of the survey: Two-thirds of Internet users look online for information about a specific disease or medical condition. The Internet has also become an important source of emotional support for people with health problems. Susannah Fox says one in five Internet users has gone online to find other people who have the same condition. It was more popular among pe...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true of Dr. Livingston's software?", "options": ["It cuts down medical expenses.", "It decreases the time spent on medical care.", "It takes doctors closer to their patients.", "It gives patients a medical test online."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2954, "question": "The southwest of Australia has been named as one of 25\"hot spots\" for future species extinction because of global warming.A new study says global warming will become a top cause of extinction across the world,with thousands of species of plantsand animals likely to be wiped out in the coming decades. According to the study,global warming ranks among the most serious threats to the planet's biodiversity and,under some conditions,may be more than that due to deforestation.This study provides even stronger scientific evidence that global warming will result in catastrophic species losses across the planet.Last month,a UN study said humans were responsible for the worst extinction and urged extra efforts to reach a UN target of slowing the rate of losses by 2010. Scientists disagree about how ...\n\nQ: According to the passage,all the 25\"hot spots\"-------- .", "options": ["are rich in plants and animals", "are lacking in natural resources", "lost most of their plants in 2010", "will be much hotter than the rest of the world"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1409, "question": "Amazingly, US crime figures have been falling for 20 years now. Of course, the big question is, why? And can any lessons be learnt? One reason could be the fall in the demand for the drug crack. During the 1980s, drug-related crimes soared, mostly caused by desperate crack users. However, according to professor Blumstein, co-author of The Crime Drop in America, news of the dangers of crack use caused its decrease and led to a fall in the number of drug-related crimes. Some say that the adoption of a zero-tolerance policy in many cities has helped lead to a fall in crime. In New York City, for example, mayor Rudy Giuliani imposed strict and automatic punishments for all crimes, including minor offences such as graffiti and littering. Many believe this has had a very strong deterrent effect....\n\nQ: By writing this article, the writer intends to tell us   _  .", "options": ["the amazing fact that US crime figures are going down", "the recent statistics showing that crime rates are falling in the US", "the answers to the question why US crime figures are falling", "the special policies adopted by the US police that help a drop in crime"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1800, "question": "Good state is when your body and mind are in the best condition for learning. These pages describe that state. Applying this information will increase your learning performance, without using any of the other techniques on this site. You will learn faster if your cells, body and mind are in good condition, or good \"state.\" Being in good state doesn't just increase your memory and learning performance. Being in good state also helps improve your health and well-being, with resulting benefits in many other areas of your life.The state described on these pages leads to peak condition for performing well in many human endeavors, from flying a plane to playing football. I've grouped the major contributors to Memletic State into three layers. These are the cell, physical and mental state layers....\n\nQ: According to the passage, to get a good lerning state, the most important thing is   _  .", "options": ["to have enough food and water", "to take exercise every day", "to listen to music every day", "to ask the experts for advice"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1891, "question": "108 cities in China took part in World Car Free Day on Saturday to promote environmentally-friendly transport and ease increasingly grid-locked city streets.It's a highlight of a nationwide urban public transport week.People were urged to take public transport,ride bikes or walk. To help out,more than 200 new buses took to the streets.And the Beijing Subway laid on 10 more trains for rush hour. A Beijing resident said, \"Today is Car Free Day,and I do find the traffic much better and the bus can go much faster.\" Another resident said,\"I spent only half an hour to go to work.It took me twice as long before. And I can find seat on the bus today.\" But in some areas not signed up for traffic control,endless lines of cars can still be seen. Some people say they just can't do without their cars. ...\n\nQ: The best title of the passage is possibly\"_\".", "options": ["Private cars are banned in cities", "Car Free Day pushes\"green\"transport", "Residents can't do without cars", "Residents should ride bikes on Car Free Day"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1884, "question": "The man from the west stopped and drew back his arm. \"You're not Jimmy Wells,\" he said in a quick and angry way, \"Twenty years is a long time, but not long enough to change a man' nose from a Roman to pug.\" \"It sometimes changes a good man into a bad one,\" said the tall man, \"you've been under arrest for ten minutes. Silky Bob. prefix = st1 /Chicagothinks you may have dropped over our way and phones us she wants to have a word with you. Going quietly, are you? That's sensible. Now before we go to the station here's a note I was asked to hand you. You may read it here at the window. It's from Patrolman Wells.?\" The man from the West opened the little piece of paper handed him. His hand was steady when he began to read, but it trembled a little by the time he finished. The note was rather sh...\n\nQ: We can suppose Jim   _  .", "options": ["was afraid of the man from the West", "got another man to help him when necessary", "had an appointment with Bob 20 years ago", "had something else to do and couldn't come himself"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3207, "question": "People want action on noise, a recent public meeting in Brisbane showed.Some want technical improvements such as quieter air conditioners or better sound barriers around major roads.Others want tougher laws to restrict noise from building sites or to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs.But the highest priority was a noise complaints system that works. Brisbane City Council receives more complaints about noise than all other problems put together.So it conducted a survey and found that about half its residents are upset by noise in one form or another -traffic, mowers, pool pumps, air conditioners or loud parties.This inspired the Council to bring together more than 100 citizens one evening to talk through a range of options. The meeting found the present regulatory syste...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that    _   .", "options": ["the Brisbane residents were satisfied with the present noise regulatory system", "many people in Brisbane preferred to live near a pub to which they have easy access", "nearly all the inhabitants in Brisbane were bothered by noise in one form or another", "noise pollution is the most serious among pollution complaints in Brisbane"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 336, "question": "Water is very important to living things. Without water there can be no life on the earth. All animals and plants need water. Man also needs water. We need water to drink, to cook our food and to clean ourselves. Water is needed in offices, factories and schools. Water is needed everywhere. There is water in seas, rivers and lakes. Water is found almost everywhere. Even in the desert part of the world, there is some water in the air. You can not see or feel it when it is a part of the air. The water in the seas, rivers and lakes is a liquid, the water in the air is a gas, and we call it water vapour . Clouds are made of water. They may be made of very small drops of water. They may also be made of snow crystals . Snow crystals are very very small crystals of ice. Ice is frozen water. It is...\n\nQ: Clouds are made of  _", "options": ["seas, rivers and lakes", "blocks of ice", "very small drops of water or snow crystals", "solid, liquid and gas"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1982, "question": "UNICEF reports that 40 million children below the age of 15 suffer from abuse and neglect. The USA National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse finds 3 million new reports of child abuse or neglect every year. According to such information on human rights abuses of children, the United Nations declared 2010 as the International Year of Youth. In answer to the common human rights abuses of young people, Dr. Mary Shuttleworth of Youth for Human Rights International(YHRI) recently completed her seventh annual World Tour to five continents in eighty days. The purpose of the tour is to promote the to tens of thousands of children and officials. According to UNICEF, 1.2 million children are illegally traded all over the world every year. Sold as goods, these children are forced into inhuman labor, ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the YHRI World Tour 2010    _   .", "options": ["has almost stopped the child abuse", "has reached different areas and people", "has found more forced child labor", "was neglected by some political leaders"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2270, "question": "The students in America usually begin high school at the age of 13 or 14. Some leave at the age of 16. But most finish the 4-year high school study. They do not get their first full-time work or begin college studies until they are 17 or 18 years old. The high school day is about 7 hours long. Part of the day is made into classes of about 50 minutes long. The students have lunch in the middle of the day. American students study English, history, math, science, art and languages. Some also learn job skills. They can learn how to use a computer or how to mend a car. Other students may learn by working in an office, a hospital or other places one day a week. Jean Wilton Anderson is 16 years old. She lives with her parents and two younger brothers in Bethesda, Maryland, near Washington D.C. Je...\n\nQ: Jean Wilton Anderson   _  .", "options": ["has a four-people family", "lives in the city of Washington", "has studied in the high school for 3 years", "drives her own car at the age of 16"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1554, "question": "There have been many great inventions, which have changed the way we live. The first great invention was one that is still very important today---the wheel. This made it easier to carry heavy things to travel long distances. For hundreds of years there were few inventions that have made as much effect as the wheel. There was little unknown land left in the world. People didn't have to explore much any more. They began to work to make life better instead. In the second half of the 19th century many great inventions were made. Among them were the camera, the electric light and the radio. These all became a big part of our life today. The first part of the 20th century saw more great inventions. The helicopter in 1909. Sound movies in 1926. The computer in 1928, and jet planes in 1930. This w...\n\nQ: The first great invention ever known was   _  .", "options": ["the camera", "the wheel", "the electric light", "the radio"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2433, "question": "May 28 (Reuters Life!) - A Japanese university is giving away Apple Inc's (AAPL.O) trendy iPhone to students for free, but with a catch: the device will be used to check their attendance. The project, which is being tested ahead of its formal launch in June, involves 550 first and second year students and some staff of a department at Aoyama Gakuin University, which is located just outside Tokyo in Sagamihara city. The school's iPhones are meant to create a mobile information network between students and professors, but they are also a convenient way for the teachers to take attendance in class. As students enter the room, instead of writing their name on a sheet, they simply type in their ID number and a specific class number into an iPhone application. To prevent students from logging in...\n\nQ: The news report mainly tells us that   _", "options": ["Iphone has got well developed in Japan", "Iphone is to take attendance at Japanese universities", "Iphone has been accepted by many students", "Iphone is free of charge at Japanese universities"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1007, "question": "No matter where you travel in Asia, you'll find yourself faced with a new culture. You can start your Asian exploration by visiting some of these attractive cities first. Beijing, China Beijing is the second largest city in China and serves as the capital. The city is so old, in fact, that almost every building has some sort of cultural or historic features -- no matter how small. Getting around the city you'll find yourself faced with amazing temples , the largest palaces in the world, and many works of art that leave you breathless. Siem Reap, Cambodia Siem Reap is the capital city of Siem Reap Province in northwestern Cambodia. Siem Reap has a lot of French and Chinese-style architectures. In the city, there are traditional dance performances, silk farms, fishing villages and a bird san...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["the cities are all capital cities now", "Beijing is the largest city in China", "one can't find a good hotel in Kathmandu", "all the cities have their own stories"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3191, "question": "An American research company shows that $248.7 billion online sales are expected by 2014. It seems as if we can't get enough of spending money through countless online clicks today. Following are some of the incredible things that you can buy online! 1) Parents 51-year-old Michael Amatrudo from Connecticut put a posting on Craig list in 2009 to sell his elderly parents, asking for $155 in return. 2) Chewing Gum Bidding for Britney Spears' chewing gum reached $14,000 in 2004. The pop star's half-eaten sandwich also went for over $500. 3) Kidney Stone Star Trek actor William Shatner sold his kidney stone for $20,000 when he put it up for sale online to see how much a piece of him was worth. He ended up giving the money to charity. 4) An Imaginary Friend This imaginary guy went (or might stil...\n\nQ: According to the text,   _   is most likely to have starred in a film.", "options": ["Britney Spears", "William Shatner", "Jon Malipieman", "Fidel Castro"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1757, "question": "Having spent five years searching for her older brother, Miss Lund was unbelievable to think she had been working in the same building for five months. Mr.Philips, 33, and Miss Lund last saw each other almost twenty years ago after their father, also called Stephen, 56, lost contact with his son from a previous relationship.Miss Lund, only five at that time, moved to India with her father and mother Rose, while Steven lived with his mother in Wolverhapton. By the time Miss Lund and her parents returned to Leeds, the family had lost all contact with Mr.Philips.On turning 18, Lund started to track down her long-lost half brother, even asking customers at the shop where she worked.But despite checking on Internet sites such as Friends Reunited and MySpace, it wasn't until the pair started wor...\n\nQ: What made Miss Lund finally believe Mr.Philips was her brother?", "options": ["The names of their parents", "His appearance", "Her friends advice", "Their talk with each other"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 290, "question": "The Queen's English is now sounding less upper-class, a scientific study of the Queen's Christmas broadcasts has found. Researchers have studied each of her messages to the Commonwealth countries since 1952 to find out the change in her pronunciation from the noble Upper Received to the Standard Received. Jonathan Harrington, a professor at Germany's University of Munich, wanted to discover whether accent changes recorded over the past half century would take place within one person. \"As far as I know, there just is nobody else for whom there is this sort of broadcast records,\" he said. He said the noble way of pronouncing vowels had gradually lost ground as the noble upper-class accent over the past years. \"Her accent sounds slightly less noble than it did 50 years ago. But these are very...\n\nQ: The Queen's broadcasts were chosen for the study mainly because  _  .", "options": ["she has been Queen for many years", "she has a less upper-class accent now", "her speeches have been recorded for 50 years", "her speeches are familiar to many people"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 366, "question": "Throughout the world, clothing has many uses. It is used to provide protection from cold. It is also worn to prevent others from seeing specific parts of one's body. However, the parts of the body that must be covered vary widely throughout the world. Some clothing is worn to provide supernatural protection. Wearing a lucky shirt to take an exam is calling for supernatural assistance. People in all cultures use clothing and other forms of bodily decoration to communicate status , intentions and other messages. In North America, we dress differently for business and various leisure activities. North American women usually are much more knowledgeable of little difference in messages communicated by clothes than men. At times, this leads to silly mistakes of understanding of female intentions...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the behavior of others towards you can be changed by your  _  .", "options": ["age", "dress", "status", "gender"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1344, "question": "Pleasant Goat, lazy Goat, Beautiful Goat and Slow Goat, which one is your favorite? The second movie of the Chinese cartoon series of Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf again achieved noticeable box office takings in china, earning more than 40 million yuan merely three days after its debut . Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf is no doubt the most successful\"China made\"cartoon series recently. It is shown on TV almost every day and its core product can be seen almost in every child's goods store. It is the Chinese Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck. The cartoon series is not only welcomed by children, but is also often discussed among adult audiences. Pleasant Goat is appreciated for his courage and wisdom. While Big Big Wolf is considered a model husband though he is usually the bad guy in the story, a...\n\nQ: Big Big Wolf is_to goats.", "options": ["kind", "bad", "friendly", "good"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2681, "question": "Due to climate change, Arctic ice is breaking up earlier in the spring, and its area is decreasing. This is creating problems for polar bears that make their homes off northern Alaska and in Hudson Bay. Polar bears off Alaska normally hunt and raise their young on ice sheets that float on the ocean. But as the ice has melted, the polar bears have been forced to spend more time on land. There, they have begun to frequent beaches, feeding on the remains of whales caught by native hunters. For polar bears, this food is less nutritious than seals that they normally catch on ice sheets. The shrinking ice has also forced more polar bears into the ocean. In the past, they only had to swim short distances between ice sheets. But as the ice has shrunk, polar bears have been forced to swim longer an...\n\nQ: What is Arctic ice doing earlier each year?", "options": ["It's freezing.", "It's hardening.", "It's melting.", "It's expanding."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1671, "question": "In 1905, as part of his Special Theory of Relativity, Albert Einstein published the point that a large amount of energy could be released from a small amount of matter. This was expressed by the equation E = mc2. But bombs were not what Einstein had in mind when he published this equation. In 1929, he publicly declared that if a war broke out he would \"refuse to do war service, direct or indirect....\" His position would change in 1933, as the result of Adolf Hitler's coming into power in Germany. Einstein's greatest role in the invention of the atomic bomb was signing a letter to President Franklin Roosevelt urging that the bomb be built because some physicists feared that Germany might be working on an atomic bomb. Among those concerned were physicists Leo Szilard and Eugene Wigner. But t...\n\nQ: We can conclude that Einstein   _  .", "options": ["assisted with the invention of atomic bomb", "directly participated in the invention of the atomic bomb", "was not involved in the invention of atomic bomb at all", "contributed to the invention of atomic bomb"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2625, "question": "The story of Juno and Lucas is one of the most touching stories about the amazing relationship between humans and their companion animals. Juno is a Belgian Malinois . The dog was beautiful but was given up by its owners, as they did not want to take on the responsibility. Lucas, a little boy, had a strange illness, a condition that stops the body's ability to process enzymes .As his life continues, he will lose the ability to speak and his physical and mental abilities will degrade till he is left in a vegetative state. The average life expectancy for the patients is 15 years. Chester, the boy's father, wanted his child to enjoy his life on earth as much as possible and looked into getting a service dog for the child. However, Lucas wasn't a good candidate due to his deteriorating abiliti...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Unlucky boy, lucky dog", "A love for a dog, a companion for a boy", "A faithful friend--Juno", "Love me, love my dog"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 230, "question": "Nothing is more frustrating than not being able to sleep, tossing and turning . Your mind is racing, going over everything that happened that day. Night noises keep you awake. What can you do? Here are some things you can do to help you to fall asleep. Sleep only when sleepy This reduces the time you are awake in bed. If you can't fall asleep within 20 minutes, get up and do something boring until you feel sleepy. Don't expose yourself to bright light while you are up. The light tells your brain that it is time to wake up. Don't take naps This will ensure that you are tired at bedtime. If you just can't make it through the day without a nap, sleep less than one hour, and take a nap before 3 p.m. Get up and go to bed at the same time every day Even on weekends! When your sleep cycle has a r...\n\nQ: _   can help you fall asleep at night.", "options": ["Reading an uninteresting story", "Thinking over what happened during the day", "Sitting quietly with the light on", "Taking some exercise"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1783, "question": "The father's role in the family is important. One researcher says babies cared for by their fathers have greater cognitive development at one year of age than babies not cared for by their fathers. Another expert reports that by spending time with their pre-school children, fathers can help to develop children's language ability. Researchers also point out that for school-age children, fathers are one link with the outside world. Fathers who value education have children who do better in school than those children whose fathers don't value education. What's more, fathers who spend quality time with their children may give their children happy memories which may last a lifetime. While each father is a unique person who educates children in his own style, good fathers have something in commo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we can find that   _   .", "options": ["fathers are more important than mothers in the family", "all fathers have the same way of educating their children", "fathers' involvement is the most important factor in children's development", "fathers have an important influence on their children from infancy through adulthood"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 782, "question": "Wood Buffalo National Park Wood Buffalo National Park is Canada's largest national park and one of the largest in the world. Established in 1922 to protect the last remaining herds of bison in northern Canada, it now protects an outstanding example of Canada's Northern Boreal Plains. The park was designated a World Heritage Site in 1983. Phone: (780) 697-3662 E-mail: wbnp.info@pc.gc.ca Banff National Park of Canada Banff's rich history dates back to 1885, when three railway workers stumbled upon hot mineral springs surfacing from deep within the mountains. This discovery led to the establishment of Banff National Park, and marked the beginning of Canada's national park system. Spanning 6,641 meadows and rivers, Banff National Park is one of the world's premier destination spots. Phone: (40...\n\nQ: Why was Banff National Park built?", "options": ["Because there were no national parks in Canada then.", "Because hot mineral springs were found in Banff.", "Because there were many valleys and mountains.", "Because there were lots of scenic islands."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1368, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the most suitable title for this passage?", "options": ["Tom And His Fellows", "The Happy Whitewasher", "Whitewashing A Fence", "How To Make The Things Difficult To Get"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3126, "question": "In the last 500 years nothing about people--not their clothes, ideas, or languages has changed as much as what they eat. Chocolate drink was first made from the seeds of the cacao tree by South American Indians. The Spanish introduced it to the rest of the world during the 1500s. And although it was very expensive, it quickly became popular, In London, shops where chocolate drinks were served became important places. Some still exist today. The potato is also from the New World. Around 1600, the Spanish brought it from Peru to Europe, where it soon was widely grown. Ireland became so dependent on it that thousands of Irish people starved when the crop failed during the years of 1845--1846, and thousands more were forced to go to live in America. There are many other foods that have travele...\n\nQ: In 1845, thousands of Irish people were forced to live in America mainly because   _  .", "options": ["Ireland became dependent on the potato", "the potato was brought to Europe from Peru", "they could easily get potato in America", "the production of potatoes reduced"], "answer": 3}]